SHE JUST WANTS TO BE BEAUTIFUL
SHE GOES UNNOTICED‚ SHE
KNOWS NO LIMit is
SHE CRAVES ATTENTION‚
SHE PRAISES AN IMAGE
SHE PRAYS TO BE SCULPTED
BY THE SCULPTOR
HEY I am JUST CARMEL
FRANCESSA
MILES
MYRON
MARNEY
FLORENCE
SHAVON
JOANNA
CHRISTINA
JOSH
KYLIE
MIRANDA
JOAD
GRACE
JAMES
TASHA
SEE THE LIGHT THAT′S SHINING
DEEPER THAN THE EYES CAN FIND IT‚
MAYBE WE HAVE MADE HER BLIND
SO SHE TRIES TO COVER UP HER
PAIN AND CUT HER WOES AWAY
CAUSE COVERGIRLS DON′T CRY
AFTER THEIR FACE IS MADE
BUT THERE′S A HOPE THAT′S WAITING
FOR YOU IN THE DARK
YOU SHOULD KNOW You are BEAUTIFUL
JUST THE WAY YOU ARE
AND YOU DON′T HAVE TO CHANGE A THING
THE WORLD COULD CHANGE it is HEART
NO SCARS TO YOUR BEAUTIFUL‚
We are STARS AND We are BEAUTIFUL
MY PEERS AND THEN THERE WAS ME.
A LOT OF PEOPLE AREN′T AFRAID
TO GIVE THEIR OPINIONS
WHETHER They are HURTFUL OR NOT.
PEOPLE WOULD LAUGH AND STARE.
PEOPLE WATCHING YOU EAT AND
MAKING LITTLE COMMENTS.
AS I GREW UP THINKING THAT I
HAD TO LOOK A CERTAIN WAY.
I NEVER THOUGHT I WAS AS PRETTY
AS THE OTHER GIRLS.
BE PROUD‚ I SHOULDN′T BE
TRYING TO HIDE IT.
OH‚ OH‚ OH
oh oh‚ OH‚ OH
AND YOU DON′T HAVE TO CHANGE A THING
THE WORLD COULD CHANGE it is HEART
NO SCARS TO YOUR BEAUTIFUL‚
We are STARS AND We are BEAUTIFUL
SHE HAS DREAMS TO BE AN ENVY‚
SO She is STARVING
YOU KNOW‚ COVERGIRLS EAT NOTHING
SHE SAYS BEAUTY IS PAIN AND THERE′S
BEAUTY IN EVERYTHING
WHAT′S A LITTLE BIT OF HUNGER?
I CAN GO A LITTLE WHILE
LONGER‚ SHE FADES AWAY
WHAT I LOVE ABOUT PEOPLE IS
WHEN They are JUST BEING
THEMSELVES‚ AND NOT WORRYING
ABOUT WHAT THEY LOOK LIKE.
EYELASHES AND MY HAIR EXTENSIONS‚
THAT′S YOU ALWAYS WANT
WHAT YOU DON′T HAVE
It is BEEN SOMETHING I have STRUGGLED
WITH MY ENTIRE LIFE.
NOT FEELING LIKE I FIT IN.
SHE DON′T SEE HER PERFECT‚
SHE DON′T UNDERSTAND She is WORTH IT
OR THAT BEAUTY GOES DEEPER
THAN THE SURFACE‚ OH‚ OH
SO TO ALL THE GIRLS THAT′S HURTING‚
LET ME BE YOUR MIRROR
HELP YOU SEE A LITTLE BIT CLEARER
THE LIGHT THAT SHINES WITHIN
THERE′S A HOPE THAT′S WAITING
FOR YOU IN THE DARK
YOU SHOULD KNOW You are BEAUTIFUL
JUST THE WAY YOU ARE
AND YOU DON′T HAVE TO CHANGE A THING
THE WORLD COULD CHANGE it is HEART
NO SCARS TO YOUR BEAUTIFUL‚
We are STARS AND We are BEAUTIFUL
HOLD ON AND JUST WAIT UNTIL YOU
CAN GET OUT OF THAT BUBBLE.
BECAUSE THE THINGS THAT
SEEM LIKE WEAKNESSES‚
THAT SEEM LIKE WEIRD THINGS
THAT MAKE YOU STRANGE‚
WHEN YOU BECOME AN ADULT AND
GET OUT INTO THE WORLD‚
You are GONNA FIND OUT THAT
ALL THOSE DIFFERENCES‚
They are LIKE YOUR GREATEST STRENGTHS.
OH‚ OH‚ OH
oh oh‚ OH‚ OH
AND YOU DON′T HAVE TO CHANGE A THING
THE WORLD COULD CHANGE it is HEART
NO SCARS TO YOUR BEAUTIFUL‚
We are STARS AND We are BEAUTIFUL
NO BETTER YOU THAN THE
YOU THAT YOU ARE
NO BETTER LIFE THAN THE
LIFE We are LIVING
NO BETTER TIME FOR YOUR
SHINE‚ You are A STAR
OH‚ You are BEAUTIFUL‚
OH‚ You are BEAUTIFUL
A LOT OF IT WAS IN MY OWN
HEAD I REALIZE NOW.
INAUDIBLE. THERES ALWAYS SOMEONE
THAT′S UNIQUE NOW‚
WHICH IS WHAT THE COOL PART‚
AND THAT′S WHAT MADE ME
COMFORTABLE TO REALIZE
THAT EVERY SINGLE PERSON IS DIFFERENT.
PERSONALITY OUTSHINES EVERYTHING ELSE
AT THE END OF THE DAY
WHAT ONLY MATTERS IS WHAT
I THINK OF MYSELF
AND THAT EVERYONE HAS DIFFERENT
KINDS OF BEAUTY
SMILE. SMILE.
OH‚ OH‚ OH
oh oh‚ OH‚ OH
AND YOU DON′T HAVE TO CHANGE A THING
THE WORLD COULD CHANGE it is HEART
NO SCARS TO YOUR BEAUTIFUL‚
We are STARS AND We are BEAUTIFUL